A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2013:052, SG 2 FA1323
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2013:052, SG 2
2005-2010
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1323
5.76 Cubic Feet Four standard record storage boxes, 1 card file box, and one letter document box.
Scope and Contents
This accession contains grant administration files, program files and associated meeting records, conferences, and briefings pertaining to the Alliance for Health Reform, 2005-2010.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Original order. Records remain as received.
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20050606), 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- Alliance for Health Reform (20050606), 2013:052:010-2013:013:020; 10 Digital Items
  Conditions Governing Access
  Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please consult a RAC archivist for further instruction.
- Alliance for Health Reform (20050606) - Oriental A, 2013:052:001-2013:052:009; 9 Audio/Visual cassette tapes
  Access copy currently unavailable. Please consult a RAC archivist for further instruction.
- Alliance for Health Reform, Oriental A, 2008; 14 Digital items
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20050608), 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20050608) - Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, 2006 January 12-14 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20050609), 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080339), 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080339) - Commission Meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System Meetings, 2009 July (Box 1, Folder 13-24)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System, 2008 November 18-19 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System, 2009 March 31-April 2 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20090558), 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20090558) - Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, 2010 January 15-17 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20090558) - Grant Report and Attachments (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20090559), 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20090559) - Briefings, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 32-34)
- CMWF Congressional Retreat binder materials, 2010; 2013:052:036; 1 Digital item
- Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, 2009 January 10-12 (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080340), 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080340) - Congressional Retreat, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 38-42)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080341), 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080341) - Congressional Retreat, 2009 February 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 44-45)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080341) - Health Policy Seminars and Professional Staff (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20080341) - Briefings, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 47-49)
- Philadelphia Comm Meeting, 2009 March 31-April 2; 2013:052:035; 1 Digital item
- Frontline, Sick Around the World, 2013:052:037; 1 Digital item
- Commission on a High Performance Health System Meetings, 2007 March 28-30 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System Meetings, 2007 July 18-20 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070528), 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070528) - Commission Meetings (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System Meetings, 2007 November 15-16 (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System Meetings, 2008 April 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System Meetings, 2008 July 22-24 (Box 4, Folder 58-59)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070529) - Congressional Retreat, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 60-62)
- Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, 2008 January 10-12 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20070530) - Briefings and Bipartisan Health Policy Retreat, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 64-66)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Briefings, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 67-70)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20060622) - Briefings and Staff Retreat, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20060621) - Congressional Retreat, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 72-77)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20060620) - Meetings (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20060622) - Congressional Staff Retreat, 2007 February 21 (Box 4, Folder 79-80)
- Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, 2007 January 12-14 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Briefings, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 82-84)
- Grant materials, 2013:052:036-2013:052:087; 49 Digital Items